[Music]
when I first started my policy like 10
years ago my first policy I was just
making like
$192,000 but I spoke with an agent and
she explained to me that just let me
know how much you can put a side and
that policy was for specifically for my
daughter's education when she goes to
the college so she told me even with $90
or $100 a month you can still get a good
sum which can pay for Education after 20
years I was diagnosed with um polycystic
kidney when I went back to my old
company the insurance company had the
medical policy they turned me down they
say no because of my current condition
there's no way I can upgrade my plan or
Hance my plan so I went back to Manu
life and I actually managed to get
myself covered with a higher loading but
they did manage to cover me on medical
and my on my current condition I guess
ultimately man life has given me a peace
of mind even if something happens to me
now or if I'm going to retire or for my
children's save education everything is
covered so many life has given me a
extremely good peace of mind without any
burdens or anything which I need to
worry
about I'm not a person who can save
money in the bank so I rather put it
somewhere where I know I can't take it
in any situ situation so always money
grows as time grows even there some of
my policies I can still take out cash I
told myself I told my agent don't tell
me that I can take out cash in my mind I
can't take out until I'm 50 or 55 years
old if you start taking out then your
Investments and the it goes down so you
don't get so much when you want to when
you're
retiring now I'm young and I'm still fit
I can still work and everything another
20 years down the road when my kids are
ready to go to college and University I
might not be healthy so having a backup
plan and saving somewhere it's always
good policies with manual life doesn't
only cover me but cover my three kids my
parents my husband all of them I know
that I will retire in a in a peaceful
mind without any financial burden or
whatever manual life Retirement
Solutions secure today secure
tomorrow visit our website to find out
more